Since I was little,I've had a question in my mind.
Why am I only myself and not someone else?
I'm aware that
"I think, therefore I am"
are the words of a great ancient philosopher,
but when I thought, I thought about someone else,
that perhaps the other person was myself, too.
Think about others.
When I did that,
I turned into someone else...
...but for no more than five seconds.
Furthermore, for the duration,
my body completely lost consciousness
and just collapsed wherever I stood.
I often found myself injured in some way.
And I could only possess someone   that was within my line of sight,
so I couldn't use it for lewd things.
I mostly possessed people who pissed me off,
picked a fight with a stranger, and returned to myself.
That kind of retaliation was all I could use this for.
Oh, that's funny!
Huh?
You bastard! What the hell are you doing?
But finally, I came up with a brilliant idea
that could take full advantage of my special ability.
Hmm.
You have five minutes left.
I could possess one smart person in class after another,
memorize their answers, and fill in my answers after returning.
Of course, I was planning on attending   a very prestigious high school.
However, unlike the normal test,
I didn't know who was intelligent during an entrance exam.
And so I snuck into top‐rated cram schools,
one after another, pretending to be   one of the students attending there.
Which students applied to which schools
and which subjects were they best at?
I researched all of that thoroughly.
I found one student after another
vying to enter the same school I was
that I could possess and take answers from.
And I was admitted to an elite high school.
[man] Now a word from the representative for new students.
‐Yu Otosaka, please come up.
‐Yes.
So that means he's the very top of the class.   ‐And he's good‐looking, too.
Today, for us new students,
you have organized a grand  ceremony to welcome us here,
and we are deeply grateful.
Wrapped in the warm rays of the spring sunshine...
[Hey, hey!
‐Huh?   ‐He's really good‐looking, isn't he?
Yeah. He might even be your type.
My type, huh?
Well, I think you think he might be your type, too!
‐Humph!
On behalf of all of us,
thank you for the opportunity.
Hmm.
This again.
This is happening more and more often.
Not only am I at the top of the class academically,
I'm one of the more attractive.
It's impossible to not be popular.
Sheesh! I'll just hurry them all on home.
I'm sorry for calling you all the way out here.
Don't worry about it.
So, what did you want from me?
I, um... I'm fine starting as just friends.
But can you maybe think about dating me, please?!
The thing is,
in order to keep my grades up at where they are now,
I have to shave time from sleep to keep studying.
I don't have the luxury of relationships.
So... I'm sorry.
Of course that's a pack of lies.
I don't study at all, ever.
Oh, I see.
I understand.
I'm sorry for calling you out like this so suddenly.
There's no way I would ever choose
a plain, normal girl like you.
The one I'm after...
‐You mean you didn't watch that TV special last night?
‐Huh‐uh.
...is the madonna of this school, of course.
Yumi Shirayanagi.
I will make... you mine!
I know I'll definitely get a chance.
It all lies in how I use the five seconds,
which are the limits of my ability.
That's it!
‐So then I...
‐Huh?
Mitchon, what's the matter?
Did you see that? She almost got run over.
Huh?
It looks like the airbag saved him.
I'm so glad.
That was close, but it went according to plan.
Oh, Yumi!
Are you all right?   ‐Yeah, that was really a close one.
Yumi, you were about to be run over by a truck.
Otosaka from class one ran out and saved you.
Really? Is that true?
Yeah. Are you hurt at all?
Ow!
Let's go to the nurse. Can you walk?
Uh... yes.
Well, guess I'll go home.
Please, wait a minute!
Um, you see,
the two of us, we're just about to walk over
to our favorite restaurant to eat our favorite pancakes together.
Would you like to come with us?
Sorry, I think I'm gonna pass.
It's better to keep this among friends.
But you just put yourself in danger in order to save my life.
I'd like to properly repay that
and I'd like to talk with you a little while longer.
Whoa, I have a phone call. Who is it?
Huh? Then I'll go home right away.
Mitchon, what's the matter?
My big brother suddenly came back from Kyoto
and he apparently ordered top‐end sushi for the whole family.
So I'm leaving the rest to you two. Bye!
That was an obvious farce,
but a nice assist nonetheless, Mitchon.
Enjoy your meal !
Wait a sec, there's a special way to eat this.
‐Uh...
‐Just copy me.
If you do this, the syrup gets across the entire thing.
Then stack them up, cut them up,   and try a bite of it. cut them up, and try a bite of it.
Mmm!
Amazing. Just by changing how you eat it,
I never realized. it gets this delicious?
It's delicious every single time.
Uh... um...
The song they're playing right now is "How‐Low‐Hello," isn't it?
Huh? Hallow‐hello?
You look like you've never heard of them.
I thought every boy our age knew them really well.
So that's what's popular nowadays?
Otosaka, can we walk home together after school
or go out to eat like this again sometime?
Hmm... Sure, I guess. Why not?
I'm so glad!
I shouldn't do this out loud.
I'll hurry on over.
Yu Otosaka from class 1‐1,
please report immediately to the Student Council room.
‐I repeat...   ‐What's this?
Yu Otosaka from class 1‐1,
please report immediately to the Student Council room.
I'm Student Council President Omura.
What is it you want with me?
I'm making someone wait, so I'm hoping you can make this quick.
That is completely up to you.
This is an exact copy of your answer sheet
to the aptitude test you took the other day.
You managed a perfect score.
The same test has been placed right there.
Right here and now, try to get a perfect score again.
Huh? Why do I have to take it again?
You've been accused of possibly cheating on the exam.
If you score 90% or above, you're innocent.
It not, you're guilty.
This is ridiculous. I'm leaving now.
Regarding this, we have the support
of both the principal and the vice‐principal.
If you leave now, you will be expelled from school.
Expelled?!
Now, please begin.
All of the answers are right there.
I'll just possess him and find out what they are.
It's the only way.
He's making a fool of me!
Huh? What in the world just happened?
I don't know. It seemed like you were
just tearing whatever that was up.
We got enough.
I'm Tomori, student council president.
Of another school, though.
So, I've been recording you since you got here.
Please take a look at the video I just recorded.
and take a note of the time.
You were not looking   at Omura the moment he ripped up the answer sheet.
Yet you said he ripped it up.
Isn't that a bit strange?
I'll show you others.
You have a special ability to possess other people.
Using that, you cheat on every exam.
Isn't that right?
Th‐That's not true. It's a sleeping disease.
I suddenly get tremendously sleepy
and can't fight the urge to nod off.
You really are troublesome.
I'll show you this, then. Look.
A copy of a recent medical exam.
According to this, you have no disease.
Now, please solve the problems on the test.
I can't deal with this! Leave me alone!
There he goes.
She even foresaw that things would end up this way.
Huh? Well then. Everything from here on is my job.
Start running! Right now!
Damn it!
Are you injured?
No, I'm fine, but what's wrong with him?
Huh?
What?! What the hell is going on here?!
What the hell? What did you just do?
‐That was teleportation.
‐Teleportation?
Yes. Just like it sounds.
I instantly move to another location.
Only I can't stop where I want.
Thanks to my special ability,
I don't know how many times I've been hospitalized.
What a half‐assed ability.
So, anyway, what are you planning on doing with me now?
We are having you transferred over to our school.
Transfer?
In this world, there are many people who possess special powers.
‐You're not the only one.
‐What?
But those powers are somewhat like an illness caught during adolescence
and will disappear in due time.
Until it goes away, you will attend classes
at the Hoshinoumi Academy with us.
I already have permission from those that have parental authority over you.
‐You mean all this is...?
‐Is real.
I gotta say, you seem like you'd be popular from just your good looks.
Did you really need to play the genius by cheating as much as possible?
That's the real question here, isn't it?
But, thanks to that, you were able to get close  to that female student  you were targeting.
Damn you!
What the...? She disappeared?
‐That is her special ability.
It can't be.
How can you just become invisible?
Actually, to me it looks like
you simply stood there . and let her punch you in the face
No way. I was the only one that couldn't see her?
Right.
Her ability is to hide from visual recognition from one target.
Every other human can see her as normal.
Another half‐assed ability.
By the way, you will be
expected to serve on our student council as well.
Huh?
‐Your ability is useful,
so I'd like for you to cooperate with us.
To do what?
To threaten those that abuse their powers for no good,
just like you have.
Because that is the kind of existence we are.
[Yu, weakly] I'm home.
Oh, hi! Welcome back home, Big Brother.
Wow! What's wrong with your face?
Oh, well, I, um, had an accident in gym class?
Oh, right, we got an amazing phone call from our uncle while you were gone.
He said that you and I were immediately going to be transferred
over to Hoshinoumi Academy's middle school   and high school as scholarship students.
Is that really true, Big Brother?
Are you serious?
Yes, it's true.
Yay! This will be great for the house budget!
And uncle is sending us   lots of tasty food so that we can celebrate.
But this means that you have to transfer schools.
You're gonna have to say goodbye to all your friends.
Yeah, but we can use smart phones   to video‐chat with one another,
so it's not going to be all that big a deal.
[Yu drily] I see.
Tonight's dinner is gonna be... ta‐da!
Omelet rice: your favorite dish, Big Brother Yu.
This again?
I've told her a million times, it was only when I was little.
Congratulations to us.
All right now, let's eat.
So sweet!
Using this pizza sauce as the secret ingredient
must have been fitting for my tongue when I was just a little child.
‐How is it? Is it tasty?
‐Yeah, it's tasty.
Wow, really? It's the first time I've wanted
to eat Mom's omelet rice in a while.
Our mom, huh?
Why would I even care about someone like that?
Are you still upset?
Yeah, of course I am.
She selfishly divorced and shoved custody over to our uncle.
I don't understand much of it, but I really wish you could be more forgiving.
We don't have parents anymore.
Our only family is you and me.
I see.
But do you want to know what I sometimes think?
That there is one more family member out there somewhere.
You and I are the only siblings we have.
Are you seeing someone in your dreams?
Hmm, you're right.
But... it's a really weird feeling,
as if it was actually true.
It's totally a dream.
Hey, we've got to be up really early to move.
You should go get some sleep.
Oh, can't I have just a bit more time, please?
Ayu, you really love stars, don't you?
You can see way off into the distance,    where people will never reach, you know.
I just think that, well, that it's an amazing thing.
You know, if you keep talking only about the stars at school,
you'll end up isolated.
Really? Why is that?
In my experience,
a better strategy is to try and liven up  the conversation,
by talking about movies and TV shows instead of the stars.
Experience? Strategy?
It's OK if you don't get it. Go to sleep soon.
Roger that.
Whoa!
Wow!
This is an amazingly huge room!
Will you and I really be able to use all this space alone,
Big Brother?
‐Uh, yeah.
‐Thank you for your hard work.
I may not be much, but please allow me to help.
Hey, just let the moving company guys do it, OK?
I thought that I could at least be a little bit of help.
But I shouldn't?
Don't take their jobs away from them.
Oh, what an amazing way to look at this.
I never would have thought of that.
So, what was going on with you the other day?
That's something I can't say.
Anyway, I'm going to have to transfer over to Hoshinoumi Academy immediately.
‐Huh?
‐I can't tell you why.
It's kind of complicated.
I'm sorry.
Until this ability goes away,
I can't be authorized to travel to an area unsupervised.
If you could come out there to see me once in a while,   that would be great.
Yeah, but that's just so far away.
Maybe you can come here every so often and see me instead?
'Fraid not. I'm really sorry,
but I can't come on my own anymore.
But why?
I'm not allowed to tell you that.
I'm forced to not mention anything about any of this to others.
There's absolutely nothing I can do about it.
I'm very grateful for what you've done.
That feeling will never leave me.
However, the fact is that you and I aren't dating yet,
so for me to chase you in a one‐sided way like that
would make me feel like some kind of stalker.
I really do feel bad about that.
But I can't come see you on my own.
I understand.
From now on, let us walk our own separate ways.
What? But that means...?
I will never forget the feeling I have towards you.
You saved my life that day, and I will forever be grateful.
And that is all.
This can't...
Thank you very much for saving me like you did.
I really do appreciate it.
But this is where I bid you a fond farewell.
Best of luck to you.
I got dumped!?
Me?
Hello?
‐Excuse me, I let myself in.
Why are you suddenly here?
It's tough with just two of you.
We came here to help out.
Oh, hi.
Are all of you from the same high school as my big brother?
Yes. We're in the student council.
My name is Takajo
and this is Tomori.
Since it's after school now, we thought we should stop by  and see if we could help.
You shouldn't have bothered.
Can we help you out, please?
Of course, we'd love to have your help.
Hmm.
Yeah, petty cunning.
So let's split up and get things done.
Right!
Thank you so much.
Huh? This must be that    tasty food  our uncle sent  to congratulate us
that Ayumi was talking about.
Whaaa...?
It's all instant ramen?!
I'll pretend I never saw this.
Ayumi, can I show you a magic trick?
Oh. Yeah, Tomori.
I'd love to see one.
Now, stay right there.
I'll be back in just a second.
OK. What?
Huh?
That was amazing!
Even more amazing than the people who are on TV.
Did you enjoy that?
Don't use her ability to mess around.
You wowed her out of her senses.
If you're going to play, you have to go home.
All right, fine.
Your big brother is scary.
Well, at least I appreciate you helping us.
I guess it's time for us to excuse ourselves.
You're going home?
But I'm going to make dinner
and I'd love it if you two would stay.
We don't have enough dishes.
‐Right, if he says so.
‐Oh!
It's all right,
'cause we'll meet again.
Hmm.
Oh! "How‐Low‐Hello."
So it is a fad after all.
Ah, that's right! Yusa Nishimori, Yusarin.
‐I think she's so cute.
That something like this sells is a sign of the apocalypse.
You know what, Big Brother?
My new school is literally right next to yours,
so I think that we should walk together.
People might think I have a thing for my sister.
A thing for me?
You brought me a present?
What? No.
Hoshinoumi, sea of stars.
What an absolutely wonderful name for a school.
Yeah. It's a name that sounds like it was created
with only you in mind.
Hmm?
Hey.
That night, I had a dream.
I'm sure it was because of Ayumi's far‐fetched announcement.
But... who was that?