Hyaa!
I'm gonna go.
Wait a minute!
You're forgetting something!
Your lunch!
What's the menu today?
It's omelet rice, your favorite.
That again?!
Th‐Thanks. Now don't to be late, OK?
I won't.
Please excuse me.
Welcome to our academy.
So every single student here has some special ability?
No. Some have the possibility of having one,
and some show signs of developing one.
You transfer them here just for that?
A long time ago,   people who had special abilities like we have
could end up as guinea pigs for misguided   and sometimes cruel neuroscientists.
If you got caught, your life was basically over.
Hah! You're exaggerating.
I'm actually talking about my big brother.
To protect those with abilities,
a certain individual created the current system,
though not in time to save my big brother.
So why did you get me into this student council
and tell me I should use my powers?
The student council here is entrusted with a special mission,
and that is to seek out those with special abilities
who are on the loose, like you were,
and either protect them   or threaten them to never use their powers.
Why would I do something like that?
In return, you will be paid appropriately.
Isn't Ayumi having to   do her best to make decent meals every day
because you can't even afford to buy proper food?
My name is Yu Otosaka.
I came here from Hinomori High School.
Nice to meet you all.
So cute!
Hey. She's a first‐year, but she's student council president?
Right. In this academy, the student council president
is not determined by grade.
It goes to someone who's active and has a sense of duty
as someone with a special ability.
I see.
This is exactly the same thing as last night's dinner.
Say, Otosaka, what are you going to do about lunch today?
Well, I don't have anything.
Then let's go to the cafeteria together.
I'll show you where it is.
That would be a big help.
You're not going to invite her?
I can ask her to come along if you like.
Nah. No thanks.
Doesn't seem to be any open seats.
Then how about we buy some sandwiches
and go back to the classroom to eat?
Well, it's pretty crowded over there, too.
Just leave that part to me.
Here's where I can show off my ability.
Is it OK for you to do that?
Don't worry, it's fine.
I'll go in from the blind spot on the camera.
Though, since I'll be going by too quickly,
what kind of breads I grab will all depend on luck.
Huh?
Hey.
What was that?
An explosion?
Sorry to make you wait.
Oh, I got a rather great result this time.
A cutlet sandwich.
What?
You call that a great result with all those wounds on you?
I do wear armor under my uniform
so the wounds are never very deep, youknow.
But you're bleeding from your head!
You know, you're a pretty dangerous guy, despite how yolook.
What do you mean by that?
Wait, you have nothing but cutlet sandwiches here.
It's teleportation, you know.
You think I had time to pick and choose what I wanted?
And every single one of them is smushed.
That's teleportation.
You think I can fine‐tune how forcefully I grab merchandise
when I'm moving that fast?
His ability really is half‐assed.
She doesn't have any female friends,
even though she's the student council president?
Her special ability is to become
completely invisible to one person she chooses.
Which means that everyone other than that person can see her.
That imperfection is what caused the situation she's in right now.
Even if she had a valid reason,
what would people around her think
after seeing her use her ability to take violent actions?
On top of that, the surveillance cameras
show nothing but an ordinary fight.
As she kept doing things like that,
obviously people eventually came to hate her.
But apparently her personality wasn't like that
until she got into middle school.
Huh?
Oh. She's walking over here.
A helper will soon be showing up.
What the hell? ‐That means, everyone gather at the student council room.
Huh? How did yofigure that?
What in the world is about to begin here?
Who is this guy?
Thoughtography... right here.
Huh?
Who was that?
A comrade who tells us the location and power
of someone who possesses a special ability.
Nanba High School, We'll go stake it out.
Come on, we're leaving early.
To do what?
Some investigation, of course.
Even though we're not with the police?
If the police you mention find this person before we do,
that person's life is all but over.
Seriously?
Start asking around.
Right!
Come on, now. Let's get started.
What is it I should be doing?
Basically, ask whether anything strange has been going on lately.
Also, since the ability has been determined to be thoughtography,
it might be good to ask about any rumors that involve photographs.
Very funny.
Good luck.
What am I doing?
Those two are nothing more than a couple of lunatics.
There was someone acting suspicious.
I want you to take over his body and look through all of his belongings.
For what purpose?
To protect the one with special abilities.
Oh, fine. Which guy is it?
Damn it, you took so long, I've lost him.
Follow me!
That's the guy. ‐[suspect whimpering]
Hurry!
Damn it. Why do I have to do something like this?
Huh? Hey.
Whaaaa!
What's this? Whoa!
Hey, what are you doing with that?
Pictures of a female student.
She's rather pretty.
Next up, well, a girl in her lingerie.
This is thoughtography?
You sure use it for something stupid.
Did you take either of these pictures?
No, no. I bought them.
Then who did you buy them from?
Look, I don't intend on leaking any of what you tell me to a third party, OK?
Please just tell me the truth.
If you don't tell us now, I'll tell the girl in this photograph
that this was in your possession and that you took it.
Udoh... in class 2‐E.
Thank you very much. OK, we're going in.
We're gonna go capture Udoh from 2‐E.
Right!
Huh?
Can you tell me if Udoh has gone home yet?
[girl] Huh? No, Udoh is...
Captain, if I may excuse myself.
Yeah. Good work today.
Wow, this is a surprise. ‐[gasp]
Who are you? Where did you come from?
Who would have thought that the culprit
who takes lewd, perverted photographs like   this with his thoughtography ability
and sells them off to his classmates
is also the school's archery team captain?
Photograph? Thoughtography?
I don't know what you mean.
Forget it. One of your customers gave you up.
Oh, yeah, we took a really good look inside your locker, too.
A ton of photos came falling out so I recorded them all
on this video camera as evidence.
I can easily open something like a locker inside a clubhouse.
Why would youbdo such a thing?
Because I can make money with it, of course.
This involves your family's finances?
Your parents wouldn't be happy with you making money like this, you know.
They're sick, OK? There's nothing else I can do!
I projected you in your underwear here.
It includes your face.
If you don't want this photo distributed everywhere,
you'll forget this ever happened.
That's all thoughtography takes?
I'm impressed.
But, um, no one would ever need that.
No matter who looks at you, you're attractive.
Seriously? I got a compliment!
All right!
Yeah, so hurry up and get outta here.
Nice work.
The photo is... gone?
It's right here.
But wait, how did you...?
Oh, man!
That's checkmate.
Just give up, OK?
Pretend like none of this ever happened.
You're the worst kind of person, you know that?
So how much martial arts spirit you possess means nothing!
Just so you know, we really don't plan
on handing you over to the police or anything like that.
However, if you keep using those powers,
your life will be completely ruined.
Do you want to become an experimental subject dissected by scientists?
Dissected? ‐So this is a warning.
Those powers will disappear once your body is finished with adolescence.
As for money, earn some by working legitimate part‐time jobs.
We took care of that successfully.
Indeed, we did.
Tell me, you guys always do things like this?
Yes. So that no one   with special abilities ends up like my big brother.
I see. So what is it, exactly, that actually happened to your big brother
after he got caught by the scientists?
It's not like I'm hiding him or anything.
How about we visit tomorrow?
Huh? Visit where?
Where my big brother is now.
OK, are you ready to go?
Yeah. What about you?
I'm going to take a pass this time.
Take care.
You haven't eaten lunch yet, have you?
No.
Then let's buy station‐specific lunches at the kiosk!
I want this one!
A beef‐tongue bento box lunch
that warms up when you pull a string!
This is totally amazing!
Yeah, I know all about them.
I can't believe it, this is so embarrassing.
How can she eat like that in a situation like this?
It's bad manners, no matter how you look at it.
What's wrong? Aren't you gonna eat the sandwich yobought?
Ahhhhh...
My big brother was the first to have a special ability.
I'd just passed the middle school entrance exams
for a national university magnet school.
I did it, Mom!
I did it! I got accepted!
You really did do your best now.
That means you could end up being a doctor, or even a minister.
Yup!
Big Brother, look at this. I got accepted.
Seriously? Unlike me, you're completely amazing, you know?
No, you're much more amazing than me, Big Brother.
I heard that some of the record companies
are starting to notice what a great band you have.
Since we're poor, I want to hurry up and land myself
a major record deal so I can live on my own.
Hey, did you ever listen to that CD I lent you?
It would get in the way of my studies, so no, I haven't.
Your entrance exams are over now so listen to it.
I want to create sounds just like it and soar to the top.
I'm not really interested in rock music and stuff.
It's different. Zhiend is not rock music, it's post‐rock.
You said that before, too.
Like, I don't understand what you mean at all.
As it turned out, I wasn't able to enter that school.
I have something important to say.
I've decided to enter you both in a boarding school
so that each of you has the chance to develop your special talents.
Huh?
What do you mean?
I was just about to sign to a record label.
I'm sorry, but can't you put that off
for just a little while?
I don't get any of this!
If I can support myself, that will take the pressure off our money situation!
It's actually the reverse.
We'll be better off financially if your guys go to this school...
What do you mean, the reverse?
In the first place, Nao is good at studying,
but I'm just an idiot who only knows how to play the guitar!
I think that's exactly what they acknowledged you for.
Then is that place a specialized school for music?
What's up with us both going together?
That day, we saw my mother
grovel on the ground and beg for the first time in our lives.
My mother, who raised us for the longest time,
all by herself.
It looked like a fairly normal school,
and I immediately made a few friends.
However, every day after classes were over,
I was forced to take something like a physical exam.
We were supposedly in the same school,
but I couldn't see my brother at all.
Every time I tried to go and look for him,
my friends would always stop me from doing so.
What I didn't know was that my brother
had been turned into an experimental subject.
My brother's special ability was to make air vibrate to his will.
He used that ability during a live performance
to change the sound of his guitar in unusual ways.
That's how they found him.
Scientists believed that my brother's ability
could be harnessed to disrupt communications
or even jack the airwaves if focused correctly.
A year later, I was finally allowed to see my brother,
but he was no longer the big brother I remembered.
He couldn't even recognize that I was his little sister.
His memories were gone.
The classmates that had been keeping me away from my brother
were placed around me by the scientists
to pretend to be my friends.
The reason they were examining me every day
was because, if one sibling has an ability,
chances are that the other one will, too.
And that was the only reason.
I swore that I wouldn't trust anyone ever again.
I snuck out of that school.
What happened after you left there?
I met the one person I could truly trust,
and that's how I'm here now.
That person is...?
Oh. We're getting off here.
I'm Nao Tomori. I'm here to see my brother.
So her first name is "Nao."
He's in room 12. Go ahead.
Think it would be OK if I took him outside?
As long as you keep to our grounds, no problem.
Thank you so much.
This way.
He's here.
Hmm?
Guess the painkillers have worn off again.
Your brother.
What in the world is he doing?
He's composing.
My brother thinks that he's actually playing a guitar.
All of those grunts and groans you hear
is him singing the main melody.
Oh!
Oh, man. He ruined another comforter.
Would you like to go outside?
It's the time of day when you see the best scenery.
It's amazing.
Isn't it, though?
Yeah. But an environment this special,
how in the world did you pull it off?
It's all thanks to the one person I can trust.
He transferred my brother to the hospital
in this beautiful place free of charge.
There's actually someone out there that generous?
He shows no interest at all.
But maybe someday someone will come up with a miracle drug
that can cure this.
Nobody is doing research on how to save patients like this.
Well, why not?
For the scientists,
people that have abilities are just like batteries.
If one runs out of power,
they can just experiment with another.
There's no incentive for them to help the test subjects
that end up like this.
I'm stunned.
We don't know whether or not
something will happen to us tomorrow, either.
Now you're just talking crazy.
How about you choose your words carefully?
Sorry.
Well then, let's go back.
You're really having a hard time with all this, aren't you?
You're sympathizing?
Well, stop that. You're nothing but a dishonest cheater.
She's right.
This is unlike me.
I'm home.
I didn't think the student council would be something that keeps me this busy.
Nothing I can do about it.
Huh?
Big Brother, you're part of the student council?
You mean I didn't tell you?
This is the first I'm hearing it!
In that case, you need to eat some of my special rolling vegetable curry
to renew your energy.
If I have a special ability,
there is the possibility that Ayumi will have one, too.
If I were to be captured,
Ayumi could end up just like Tomori.
It's done!
It looks great.
I hope you really like it.
So sweet!
Uh, well, um, can it be that the secret ingredient of this curry is...
Pizza sauce: the secret ingredient of our household!
Oh, man, this tastes no different
from all the omelet rice she's made.
Wow!
I guess it's your daily routine, but hurry up and go to sleep.
I was able to see a comet today, so I'm deeply moved
and can go to sleep totally excited!
That's pretty skillful of you.
But the comet that I really want to see is a completely different one.
Oh? ‐A comet with a really long orbit!
What is that?
It's a comet that swings by us only once
every few centuries!
They have comets like that, huh?