Sorry, but I overslept this morning and ran out of time.
So it's omelet rice again.
Y‐You know, I don't need to bring lunch anymore.
Oh? Really? Why is that?
Well, most of the guys don't bring their own lunches.
They all go to the cafeteria.
I'm going to be eating with them from now on.
Too bad. I like to make your lunch.
But, since I made it today, I want you to take it with you!
Uh, sure.
There’s no way I'd be able to eat omelet rice
with a message written on it in a classroom.
Oh, good morning.
Yeah, good morning.
You seem fairly spiritless today.
No, this is about how low my spirit is all the time.
Especially mornings.
Tell you what: at lunch today, I'm gonna buy you
the limited edition beef tongue curry,
guaranteed to lift your spirits right up.
Will you make it there in time to get a limited edition?
With my ability for speed, it'll be a piece of cake.
Ah, that's right.
Huh?
Hello, I've been waiting for you. Here you go.
Right now, I think it would be better   if we got you straight to the hospital.
Oh, I'm used to this. It happens all the time.
I'm sorry to make you worry about me.
His ability is way too half‐assed.
Ahhh! A flood of spices. This is how curry should be! Delicious!
I'm glad it exceeds your expectations.
Curry is something that should be spicy, after all.
It's medium spicy, but is that the right level of spice for you?
The beef tongue melts in your mouth. It's the best!
You must really love curry.
Mm‐hmm.
I'd actually forgotten how much.
OK. I understand.
Our comrade is coming again.
We should head to the student council room.
Why does that guy always show up soaking wet?
He can't use his special ability unless   he gets soaking wet while fully clothed first.
What a cumbersome, half‐assed ability.
The ability is channeling.
What is "channeling"?
Spiritualism.
Allowing dead individuals to possess them like shamans.
Someone who can really use that   as a special ability and not just a fraud?
That’s pretty amazing.
One more: pyrokinesis.
I can't believe this person has two abilities.
I'd like to get moving and grab this one as quickly as possible.
Wait, this is an ordinary road.
And is that supposed to mean something?
It means they're on the move.
In the middle of a weekday?
Are they ditching school or something?
But this road is troubling.
It'd be much better   if it wasn't a narrow alley that's not very popular.
So, what’s the big deal?
Oh, well, we should head out there anyway.
Huh? This is the place?
Yes.
What's the matter?
It looks like that person must have been pretty desperate
when they passed through here.
How's that?
This side of the box has no dust on it.
In other words, whoever it was ran through here   and bumped into this box.
What you're saying is that you think   this person was being chased.
Sounds like there was an incident.
Another troublesome‐‐
For now we'll keep moving forward.
Two new sets of footprints.
One of them has a short stride
and the other one is quite a bit longer.
This totally indicates a girl being chased by an adult.
We have to hurry.
Oh, that thing earlier?
What was it?
They were filming something   where an idol was being chased by a big guy.
An idol?
Let's see...
Right, it was Yusa Nishimori.
I've heard that name before.
Me too.
Yusarin?!
Oh, yeah. It's the idol that Ayumi likes.
So you know her?
She's the unbelievable lead vocalist
for the band How‐Low‐Hello and an upcoming gorgeous super idol
that sings and dances like no one I've ever seen in my life!
I can't tell you what a big turnoff that is. Stop!
Her career started in the sixth grade   when she won the grand prize
in the 14th reader‐model audition for the magazine Petit Banana
and debuted as their exclusive model!
Then she landed a job as a regular member   of the "Movement Morning!" show
but quit two years later to focus on school.
She restarted her career in show biz after‐‐
Hold it. Let's get back to the point.
So that girl caused some issue with her special ability
and became a fugitive, am I wrong?
You really don't have to say   that for us to know it. ‐[Yu groans]
Her agency is Sea Rex Productions.
Wouldn't it be quicker if we just called them?
We're talking show biz here. They're not gonna tell us anything.
Then what should we do?
Let's see.
A suspicious target. I'll chase him!
Tomori!
Otosaka, use your ability!
Huh?
I'm the one who actually feels the pain,
so I'd rather you not use this tactic from now on.
This is why we get compensation.
What?
That hurt.
Damn it, what would you have done if the camcorder broke?
That's your issue?
Wake up, bastard.
Who the hell are you?
No, who the hell are you?
Tell us what we wanna know and we'll call an ambulance for you.
You realize you're headed straight to death right now?
I was just offered a job, all right?
What kind?
Sorry, I can't tell you that.
Is it something you're willing to lose your life to protect?
I'm looking for Yusa Nishimori.
And who asked you to do that?
Taiyo TV.
Right. What was their name?
I don't know the person's name. And that's the truth.
Great, understood. I'd already called for   an ambulance before you talked.
Hey. What the hell are you guys?
Just some people looking for a woman named Yusa Nishimori.
Her nickname is Yusarin!
Why are you looking?
I don't exactly know the reason why,
but it's a fact that she's being chased,   so we thought we'd help her out.
You guys know Yusa?
I'm a huge fan!
Would you stop interrupting?
I was watching you. How the hell did you defeat that guy?
We did it using special abilities.
Probably a lot like the ability Nishimori has.
How do you know about that?
If you just trust us, I believe we can help save her from harm.
I see. I'm gonna need to see some proof.
Show me that you have the same power that she does.
It's not exactly the same power, but...
What the...?
Here.
Now do you believe what I'm saying?
Yeah. Come on, I'll take you to her.
Though it's a bit confusing.
What do you mean by that?
Things got slightly complicated.
I want you guys to see for yourselves.
So this is a nightclub.
You really don't have to film all this, do ya?
This way. And don’t lag behind.
Hey, I'm back.
So how is everything outside today?
Ohh! It actually is the real Yusarin!
I have all the How‐Low‐Hello CDs.
Big turnoff!
Thanks so much, that's wonderful.
It really is the girl I saw on TV.
Hey, what is with those guys?
They're just like Misa and   have special abilities that they can use.
Wait a minute, I thought her name was Yusa,   but it's actually Misa?
That's the part that makes this complicated.
What are you doing? You sure we can trust them?
I watched them use their powers   to defeat those other guys, all right?
Is it OK if we ask her directly what's going on here?
If you ask something stupid,   you're not getting out of here in one piece.
Why you gotta be so scary?
Tomori, be really careful here.
Yeah, yeah.
It's very nice to meet you. I'm Tomori.
I'm Yusa Nishimori, nicknamed Yusarin.   It's very nice to meet you.
So she calls herself Yusarin?
This is the first time in my life I've met a real idol.
You're so unbelievably cute, you almost look like a doll.
I want to get as close to you as she is.
Hey, back off!
Now, now. So first off,   could you please tell me your actual name?
It's Yusa Kurobane.
Yeah? Well, I wasn't asking you!
Your real name sounds more like a stage name.
Yes. I hear that a lot.
But Kurobane means "black feathers,"
and it's not really suitable for an idol,
so they renamed me Nishimori.
That makes sense.
Now, there are some occasions
when you are not Yusa Kurobane.
Are you aware of that fact?
No, she's not, so how do you know about it?
I wasn't asking you, bastard.
What was that?
So, was I right about that, Kurobane?
That's exactly it. I guess you can call it sleepwalking.
I've been falling asleep without realizing it,
and then when I wake up,  I'm somewhere else, with no idea how I got there.
The doctors who examined me said there's a chance that I have
a multiple personality disorder.
Oh, they did, huh?
Well, it's not schizophrenia,   so you don't have to worry about that.
She has her own special ability just like the three of us.
Her power is to allow a dead person to possess her body.
Seriously?
I believe that the ability is calling forth this Misa girl
that you guys were talking about earlier.
Misa?
Is something the matter?
Don't ask anything.
Is it someone she knew?
Yeah, she was Yusa's older sister.
She died six months ago in an accident.
You bastard.
Don't go blabbing on about things
to some stranger you just met!
Can I assume that you're Misa?
It's so annoying how cramped it is with all of you here!
She’s totally changed.
Whoa, that's really impressive.
Calm down, Misa! You're gonna burn us all to death!
I suppose that wouldn't be good.
I'm very surprised.
It seems she can't call forth the spirit on her own
and that Misa is in control.
So you got a problem with that?
Another ability that's somehow half‐assed.
That means she has an unparalleled ability to be possessed.
And Misa, who possesses Yusa, has pyrokinetic ability.
Yeah.
So, what is your relationship with these two?
They're my friends from back   when I was alive and still causing trouble.
Do you have any idea why your little sister is being chased?
Yeah. 'Cause of this.
Yusa accidentally brought this home from some shoot.
It belongs to one of the bigger‐name producers   at the TV station.
And she accidentally read a text that was sent to it.
Stealing company money, organized crime connections.
Stuff that would get the guy arrested   if it was taken to the cops.
Did you guys think to turn the power off?
Yeah. But it was on until yesterday.
Then they probably already know
that you're hiding somewhere in this area from the GPS.
Even if you gave the phone back now, you wouldn't be safe.
And, if you gave it to the police,
it would look like Kurobane sold out the producer
and could keep her from working in show biz.
OK, I'll burn it down, station and all.
Are you stupid? You do that,   and your little sister will end up in prison!
Who the hell do you think you are, huh?
Do you really want to do something   that will land her a stint in juvenile hall?
That would make absolutely no sense.
Now please calm down. You want to save your sister, right?
Huh? Yes, of course.
Then we should help each other
turn the tables on this guy and threaten him instead.
Huh?
Can we win?
I'm really good at creating wonderfully devious plans
for threatening others, so you can trust me.
You've got spunk.
All right then, I'll do whatever you say.
I'd like the both of you to help as well.
Of course we will, if Misa says so.
Oh my, I didn't fall asleep again just now, did I?
You must be really tired, that's all, it's all right.
Why don't you have some roasted marshmallows and relax?
Oh! The marshmallows turned into freshly roasted ones.
This is unbearable.
I have no clue how I should approach Yusarin from now on.
Every picture I had in my head about her has been blown.
You're a scary guy.
First we should head to a shop that sells work clothes.
What for?
You two are going to need a set of fireproof clothing.
It's me.
Huh?
So you finally showed up.
Realize that you couldn't escape?
Um, I really don't know the reason why I'm being chased so much.
Did I do something wrong?
Give me back my phone!
Is this the one?
Yeah.
Even if I return it to you now, am I, like, still in trouble?
Whatever happens, there's no future   for you in this industry anymore.
There's no more future for me?
Bastard! The one who has no future is you!
I think I'll take out one more!
What the... What the hell's going on?
You probably thought that you had me cornered tonight,
but you didn't realize that   it was me that had you cornered all along.
You really are senseless, you know?
What the hell are you?
I mean, are you really Yusa Nishimori?
Of course, I'm Yusa Nishimori, the real Yusarin, who else?
And in order to ensure my success,
I'm willing to kill anyone who gets in my way, like them!
That hurts!
This is getting boring. I'll get rid of them all at once.
W‐Wait, wait, wait. Just a minute. Hold on, please.
Like I'm gonna wait! ‐[producer groans]
What the hell is going on here?
I can bury you in the shadows at any point I want, understand?
I get it, I give up.
Please, don't hurt me.
I'll give this back to you.
But there is no next time.
I'll eradicate you in a heartbeat.
Thank you very much for all your help.
No, you helped us.
He believed that everything that happened tonight
was done by Yusa all on her own.
That producer will never dare to go up against her again.
No, I'm afraid everything is not completely settled yet.
And so I'd like you to transfer into Hoshinoumi Academy
and do everything you do alongside us from now on.
Why would she do that?
Just like how I explained earlier.
If she gets caught by the scientists,   her days as a guinea pig will begin
and she will never be able to   return to a normal life, understand?
The condo next to our academy will be the safest place
for Kurobane to continue to grow   and live something of a normal existence.
That's a life‐saving story for Yusa.
We'll do that.
Hold on!
Then, well...
If Yusa's powers disappear,
does that also mean we'll never see Misa again?
Yeah, that's exactly what I wanted to ask.
Well, I suppose that will happen,
but she's already dead, isn't she?
Isn't it amazing that you were able to see her at all?
But
Sho, it's just like she says.
In reality, she's not here.
It's time to say goodbye and let her go.
Then at least let me tell her how I truly feel about her.
Hmm?
Well, uh... How do I put this?
Now is when I can't think of what I should say?
Huh? Sho? Did you used to have the hots for me?
Uh...
That's right.
I really loved you, Misa.
It's embarrassing to say...
but I was in love
and you passed away before I could tell you.
We had a motorcycle accident while we were riding together.
I was OK, but I was the one that killed you.
It's my fault.
I see. It's all right.
I made you harbor such immense feelings inside,
but I was the one that looked for dangerous thrills.
I reaped what I sowed.
Don't cry, that's not like you at all.
Sho, forget about me.
And starting tomorrow, live your own life.
And don't keep dragging the dead into it.
Otherwise, your life will get screwed up
and you won't be happy in the future, OK?
Jeez, you really are a troublesome boy.
Sho.
All right, Misa.
I'll walk my own path that you're not a part of.
I'll sever my feelings for you.
And that's how I'll live on.
Good. And I hope that both of you
live very long and happy lives.
Yeah.
Sure.
See ya! And thanks for everything.
'Cause it was absolutely great!
It was a really long day.
I'm exhausted.
You are so late!
If you're going to be this late,
I told you that I wanted you to call!
How about you?
What are you doing up at this hour?
Eating dinner together as a family is a rule
that's been passed down the Otosaka house for generations.
Sorry, I was busy again today   doing work for the student council.
Aww. When you say that to me, I can't say anything back.
So tell me, what is it you made for dinner tonight?
I made a very satisfying spaghetti with meat sauce.
Oh! It's How‐Low‐Hello again!
Wow, it really is the same person that I met today.
Huh? Who exactly are you talking about?
You know, Yusa Nishimori, the actual person.
You mean the real one?   So you've actually gotten to meet Yusarin?
Oh, crap! But they didn't tell me to stay quiet about this.
So I guess I can tell her.
She's transferring into my academy tomorrow.
What? Oh, that makes me so jealous!
Do you think that maybe I'll be able to meet her soon?
Well, I guess that certainly is a possibility.
Wow!
Oh, wow.
Let's start by cleaning up your nosebleed.
It's just something that's so amazing!
Come on, you're getting way too excited about this.